<document id="bone marrow">
    <sentence>About 85% of the cell population in this bone tissue are osteocytes and the remainder are osteoblasts, <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>, etc."</sentence>
    <sentence>After informed consent, <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> specimens packed with leukemic blasts were obtained in each patient.</sentence>
    <sentence>APL patients showed increased genome-wide DNA methylation with higher variability than healthy CD34+ cells, promyelocytes and remission <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>.</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> biopsy, AraC"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> biopsy, DAC"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> biopsy, mock"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> cells collected from healthy donors were sorted and DNA extracted at Washington University in St. Louis, microarrays were then run at USC"</sentence>
    <sentence><cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived mesenchymal stroma cells (MSCs) have many of the properties of multipotent stem cells, and can be differentiated towards osteoblasts in vitro, making these cells a convenient tool for investigation of osteogenesis.</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived MSC (iP-MSC)"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 00_751"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 01_1808"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 02_1505"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 02_1522"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 02_1550"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 02_723"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 03_106"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 03_1310"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 03_1380"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 04_126"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 04_6"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 05_1464"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 05_170"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 05_579"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 06_2096"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 06_518"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 06_758"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 07_1768"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 07_1962"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 07_2252"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 08_151"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 08_723"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 08_774"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 08_785"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 08_930"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 10_1420"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 10_1789"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 11_834"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, 12_254"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells, leukemia"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> MSC-derived iPS cells (iPSCs)"</sentence>
    <sentence>"<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> sample grown in cultutre"</sentence>
    <sentence>"cell description: neuroblastoma, BE-C is a clone of the SK-N-BE neuroblastoma cell line (see ATCC CRL-2271) that was established in November of 1972 from a <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> biopsy taken from a 2-year-old individual with disseminated neuroblastoma after repeated courses of chemotherapy and radiotherapy."</sentence>
    <sentence>Cells able to form bone through endochondral ossification and attract <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> in an innovative in vivo model were compared to cells lacking these capacities.</sentence>
    <sentence>"cells isolated from healthy <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"cell type: <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> mononuclear cells"</sentence>
    <sentence>"cell type: normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> progenitor cells"</sentence>
    <sentence>"CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>c-myc binding sites were associated with low methylation.</sentence>
    <sentence>CN-AML blasts isolated from patient <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> aspriation were compared to CD34+ cell population from healthy donors by DNA methylation array and affymetrix gene expression microarray."</sentence>
    <sentence>Comparing four commonly use MSC sources (<cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (BM), white adipose tissue (WAT), umbilical cord (UC) and skin) we found only <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (BM)-derived MSCs capable of endochondral ossification and marrow attraction.</sentence>
    <sentence>"Density centrifuged <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"disease state: normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"DNA was extracted from patient <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> samples and xenograft <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> samples using Qiagen Allprep kit.</sentence>
    <sentence>"Genome wide DNA methylation profiling of leukemia stem, blast cells obtained from 15 AML patients and of normal hematopoietic stem/progenitor cells from 5 normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>.</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 5729917060_RO3CO2"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 5729917060_RO4CO2"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 5729917060_RO5CO2"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 5729917060_RO6CO2"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8359018137_RO1CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8359018152_RO1CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8363800011_RO1CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8363800011_RO2CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8363800026_RO1CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> CD34+ cells 8363800026_RO2CO1"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from CMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2627"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2710"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2712"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2748"</sentence>
    <sentence>"genomic DNA from MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> ID2753"</sentence>
    <sentence>"Genomic DNA was extracted and purified from AML and normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> samples using Epicentre Kit according to standard instructions"</sentence>
    <sentence>"GMP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"HSC of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"Human fetal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> was obtained, and using flow cytometry antibodies, four populations of B-cell developmental stages including stage 1 (S1; predominantly multipotent progenitors before lineage commitment and common lymphoid progenitors), stage II (S2; pre-B-I cells), stage 3 (S3; pre-B-II cells) and stage 4 cells (S4; immature B cells).</sentence>
    <sentence>"Immortalized human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived mesenchymal stromal cell line DNA methylation [iMSC#3 (Culture I)]"</sentence>
    <sentence>"Immortalized human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived mesenchymal stromal cell line DNA methylation [iMSC#3 (Culture II)]"</sentence>
    <sentence>In conclusion, a human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived stromal cell line was developed, which can be used for basic studies of mesenchymal cells and to functionally study transgenes that might play a role in oncogenic transformation."</sentence>
    <sentence>In this paper, the generation and characterization of a TERT-immortalized, non-tumorigenic human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived stromal mesenchymal model cell line is described.</sentence>
    <sentence>"In this study, we have analyzed DNA methylation characteristics of human mesenchymal stem and progenitor cells (MSPCs) form different tissue sources including <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (BM), white adipose tissue (WAT ), umbilical cord (UC) as well as dermal fibroblasts by using the HumanMethylation450K array.</sentence>
    <sentence>"L-MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>In this study we have reprogrammed mesenchymal stromal cells (MSC) from human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> by retrovirus-mediated overexpression of OCT-3/4, SOX2, c-MYC, and KLF4.</sentence>
    <sentence>"MEP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>Mononuclear cells from the <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> were isolated using standard density centrifugation and cultured in minimum essential medium (MEM) Alpha medium (cat.</sentence>
    <sentence>"Mesenchymal stem and progenitor cells (MSPCs) from human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"MPP of normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>MSCs were subcutaneously implanted into immune-compromised mice to comparatively evaluate bone formation and subsequent <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> attraction.</sentence>
    <sentence>"normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> progenitor cells"</sentence>
    <sentence>"MSCs were isolated from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (tibia plateau) after written consent using guidelines approved by the Ethic Committee of the Use of Human Subjects at the University of Aachen (permit number: EK128/09).</sentence>
    <sentence>"Patient and donor samples were obtained either from blood or <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>.</sentence>
    <sentence>"Normal human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> cells"</sentence>
nomenon.</sentence>
    <sentence>"primary cells isolated from patient's blood or <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"sample origin: Human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived mesenchymal stromal cell"</sentence>
    <sentence>"""Reprogramming of somatic cells into induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSC) is an epigenetic phenomenon.</sentence>
    <sentence>"sample type: Remission <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"Sorted normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> cells from healthy volunteers at Washington University"</sentence>
    <sentence>Samples included 20 leukemia stem cells, 24 blast cells and 30 normal hematopoietic stem and progenitor cells (6 different types from 5 normal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>s)."</sentence>
    <sentence>"tisse source for mscs: <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (BM)"</sentence>
    <sentence>"tissue: fetal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>"</sentence>
    <sentence>"""tisse source for mscs: <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> (BM)"""</sentence>
    <sentence>"tissue: <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> / peripheral blood"</sentence>
    <sentence>To this end CMP, GMP, PMC and PMN cell populations were isolated by FACS from <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> from healthy donors and analysed by CAGE as well as expression and DNA microarrays."</sentence>
    <sentence>We here describe the pattern of gene expression, histone modification and DNA binding of the bone master regulator RUNX2 during osteogenic differentiation of an immortalized human <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type>-derived MSC cell line.</sentence>
    <sentence>"We examined DNA methylation and RNA expression status during early B-cell development by sorting multiple replicates of four separate stages of pre-B cells derived from normal human fetal <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> and applied high-dimension DNA methylation scanning and expression arrays."</sentence>
    <sentence>We reprogrammed <cell_type>bone marrow</cell_type> MSCs into iPSCs which were subsequently re-differentiated towards MSCs.</sentence>
</document>
